[Music]
so we're recording this just a few hours
after the end of the UK general election
and we don't usually cover sort of the
micro of politics on the channel we
usually sort of look at what the
underlying dynamics what the underlying
cultural dynamics are but we think this
is a really good opportunity to talk
about some of the subjects we've been
talking about on the channel cuz we
think some of the frames that we've used
can maybe hope to highlight what's been
going on for those who haven't watched
or don't follow UK politics that closely
I think a fair summary would be a
conservative landslide Boris Johnson
winning a big majority and the Labour
Party under Jeremy Corbyn going to their
lowest seat total since 1935 ley it's
it's the pretty much the I would say the
destruction of the left which is
something that's quite close to my heart
we'll talk a bit about our own political
kind of background as well in this piece
but I think what's really important for
this it's one of the meta frames one of
the bigger frames that we've been
looking at since the beginning of the
channel since a glitch in the matrix is
where progressives the Left liberals
generally go wrong what the blind spots
are and what because of whether you're
on the left or the right
a healthy left is good for a healthy
right it's good health for a healthy
politics we've been covering a lot of
different threads on the channel and it
feels like a lot of them converge in a
moment like this so we've been covering
the ongoing polarization in culture this
inability we have to talk to people who
have differing opinions related to that
is the fact that we are existing we're
spending a lot of our time in social
media filter bubbles so we're seeing
over and over people who think like us I
noticed this on Facebook today you know
the particular bubble I'm in everyone's
kind of shocked because they're you know
there's a lot of a lot of very
progressive friends and it seemed it
would seem like up until this moments
like labour was just definitely going to
whimpers we all think like this and then
it's just yet again huge upset so as
well as that there's also the the shadow
we
talk about all the time on the channel
and especially the shadow of progressive
politics in the shadow of liberalism is
that what is the what is the thing
that's not being seen that is creating
these major surprises and these major
upsets so we're gonna play a lot of
different clips and we then a lot of the
different people we've had talking about
this and then finally also what do we
need to know about our own biology what
do we need to know about our own
psychology that's playing into this so
something that often gets overlooked is
us as individuals where are we where are
we contributing to this whole Malou of
you know the world going upside down as
a lot of people see it and what can we
then do about that so yeah we'll be
playing some clips from films that we've
already put out and we'll be playing
some new material as well something from
Diane musho Hamilton amazing mediator a
Zen priest and an expert on integral
theory we've used the integral map quite
a bit in the past and Daniel SHM Acton
Berger so we had war on sense-making
a couple of months ago and that was a
big hit on the channel we've got war on
sense-making 2 coming out next week I'm
going to play a couple of clips from
that I'm gonna play one clip from him
now which I think so really for me this
whole will talk about kind of my
political biography and sort of where
I'm coming from in a minute but what
this whole especially now this this sort
of real and demolition of the Labour
Party the left in the UK and after a
really toxic election campaign where so
many people had a sense that none of the
parties really were fit for purpose like
the politics just wasn't fit for
purposes like if we accept that the
world is changing massively and changing
quickly and that we need some kind of
new synthesis which is what we've been
talking about on the channel a lot that
what would a new synthesis look like and
I think a new synthesis would involve
probably going beyond sort of fairly
outdated concepts of left and right what
the integral worldview has called a more
integral position what does a place
beyond the polarization look like we're
going to explore that a bit and I think
it's also like deeply intertwined in
thinking for ourselves and moving beyond
groupthink and tribalism and I'm going
to play Daniels clip around that cuz I
think it speaks to it perfectly
we were talking earlier about Facebook
in the way that echo chamber type
phenomena just built into algorithms can
let alone the social tribal type
dynamics that are made easier not in
person lead to echo chambers where
people think that most everyone believes
kind of the way they do because that's
what they're seeing except those bad
guys over there that are far that are
far enough away that they only get the
caricature eyes version of them the
essential thing to good sense making is
a commitment to earnestness like a
sincere profound commitment to
earnestness in our sense making which
means that the enemy of that is bias of
any kind and which means vested
interests of any kind and so the desire
to fit in my group is a source of bias
in vested interest because my group
might have things wrong or be missing
stuff so another concept but I find
really useful from Daniel schmock
hamburger is the process whereby we
outsource our sense making and I think
that's something I've seen quite a lot
of in this particular election because
to stay completely up to date with
everything that's going on requires
actually quite a bit of work requires a
lot of reading has a lot of focus I
think that level of self responsibility
is part of that new political or social
paradigm there's there's a huge amount
of as Jordan Hall is all said in the
channel a huge amount of pressure comes
or responsibility comes on the
individual and we all have to take that
responsibility we can't really anymore
be outsourcing what we think to other
people if I don't understand the partial
truths and the values that they care
about I don't have a chance at
understanding reality and if I don't
understand even beyond that why it's
compelling I don't have a chance of
possibly engaging in a constructive or
meaningful way so all I can do is
villainize them and engage in warfare
and then to various degrees win or lose
but to some degree all lose and like
that's a very very simple thing I would
suggest everyone do if you tend to be
left-leaning and most of your friends
kind of agree with you about climate
change or abortion rights or whatever I
would actually really like you to find
follow bin shapiro follow the proper
terian institute follow you know bear
follow Heritage Foundation and Cato
Institute and whatever and actually seek
to understand both where they're sharing
things that you actually didn't know and
even where you really disagree why it's
compelling with an answer that isn't
just because they're all stupid because
you actually don't have any chance of
healing a culture war otherwise you only
have a chance of engaging in it and if
someone happens to be more right
oriented and of course saying right left
is itself over simplified but we'll use
that as a simplification for all the
perspectives that are engaged in some
kind of warfare that actually need to be
engaged in some kind of more generative
dialectical conversation study
intersectionality like follow some of
the thinkers that are actually giving
arguments for and history for why some
of that's important actually read some
of the postmodern thinkers read Foucault
and Dehradun whatever before just saying
all postmodern isn't as stupid and again
look to see are there true insights and
critiques in there and can you factor
them to understand them and even where
you don't think they're true can you see
why they're compelling so we've talked a
lot on the channel about polarization
where conversations break down and it
particularly filter bubbles and I felt
that probably most keenly around this
sort of politics and especially around
the left especially around labor in the
UK so my background I was my family was
sort of labor through and through we
went to like like classic kind of
left-wing CND marches labor activists I
remember going kind of leafleting with
my dad when he was a labor activist back
in the day and so it's always kind of
been my home is the Labour Party in the
UK so I know I've gone on a bit of a
journey since but I know that psychology
really really well I know that that
tendency on the left to make judgments
about people based on their views like
that that was part of my psychology for
quite a while
when you're growing arms like that / is
that person Ettore it's that person
conservative or this sort of checklist
of the acceptable views to have and then
kind of checking against it and being
like oh is that person yeah that / is
that person good or bad this kind of
implicit kind of other ring that the
left does I think is that that that
force that is kind of run rampant says
so much about what's going wrong in
culture at the moment and in like the
the big film that kind of would pretty
much started off real wisdom glitch in
the matrix really I mean I mentioned in
that how the the post 2016 realization
had been that that's effectively what a
driven Trump and driven brexit was this
this realization that there was a
liberal worldview that considered itself
to be really really really really
compassionate but actually was very
dismissive and very judgmental towards a
whole swath of the population and was
this sort of hidden tribalism of
liberalism and that's been something
that I've got on a real journey around
and been very outspoken on Facebook like
I've been after Corbin was elected in
2015 as leader of the Labour Party and I
saw how many of the people around me how
many of my friends how many of the
people in my filter bubble were
supporting him I was like actually
filter bubbles are an existential threat
and I'm gonna start speaking out and
I've been so what I see Corbin is
amazing I'm gonna post an article below
here where someone I know a little bit
David Hirsh wrote about the politics of
core monism in 2015 I think it's still
the best thing that has ever written
about it because he basically said
Corbin ISM styles itself as being
compassionate and being inclusive and
being on the side of the many but
actually in practice what Corbin ISM
does is it other Rises anyone who
doesn't agree with their particular
narrative and their particular view on
the world and I think that's absolutely
true
I think that's been borne out by all of
the experiences I think a lot of us have
seen on social media like how toxic and
nasty the Labour Party has got for
people who are considered other that's
kind of on
deniable and also how much it had then
was widely rejected by the working
classes by all of the traditional labor
supporters labor has been decimated in
the seats where it was strongest and I
think that kind of wake-up call you have
to kind of look at that and see why has
that happened so I've been on quite a
different political journey to most of
my friends in that I started fairly
left-leaning and then started exploring
a lot of particularly libertarian ideas
anarchist ideas and started moving
increasingly to a space where it became
difficult to define is it left or right
for example I I really value individual
liberty extremely highly however I also
believe in a social safety net so I you
know saying I'm a libertarian also
doesn't feel quite accurate but what is
interesting about it for me is that on
days like today when when a lot of my
friends are gnashing their teeth and
pulling their hair out and feeling very
kind of upset about the result my I'm
not understanding why people might have
voted in that way that's the key thing I
often feel I have an understanding of
that because I share a lot of the core
values that a lot of people might be
acting on when they're voting for things
that my friends don't understand so I
think the easiest way for me that I
found to frame it is Jonathan heights
work so Jonathan height wrote a he's a
moral psychologist I think it's the best
way to describe him he wrote a book
called the righteous mind just
incredibly useful to look at well I mean
why are we so righteous about our our
political beliefs and done a lot of
research looking at the the core moral
foundations that we have and looking at
morality in general so there's a lot so
really big with liberal let's say that's
again a loaded term but liberal people
is care like caring for others which
obviously we all care about but it's
like thanks very very highly and his
point is that there are other let's say
moral tastebuds
so there's fairness cheating loyalty and
betrayal there's authority and
subversion there's Liberty and
oppression and sanctity and degradation
and conservatives tend to rank roughly
evenly
a lot of those so it becomes very
difficult for someone to from one moral
value system which you're born with in a
lot of ways you know it doesn't make you
better or worse where you land on these
no more than your sexuality makes you a
better or worse person it's just how
you're geared up and you know I
personally temperamentally I'm geared up
much higher on a lot of those other
moral tastebuds so I have a certain
understanding of okay I understand why
someone might care about being oil to
your country or why someone might care
about the sanctity of the nation-state
or whatever it might be
while I might share different politics
it it makes sense to me and what I've
noticed with this election in particular
is a lot of people in my particular
bubble just not being able to understand
how anyone could think differently how
could anyone vote conservative because
they don't care about people it's like
well everyone cares about people they
just care in different ways everyone
cares about fairness that's ingrained
all the way I mean chimpanzees that
France Duvall wrote a great book or
several great books around animal
empathy it dogs have empathy like we all
have empathy we all care about other
people we just express it in different
ways we do Express fairness in different
ways and understanding that I think is
absolutely key for this political moment
right now yeah and Jonathan Heights work
I think maps on really well to Ken
Wilbur's kind of integral framing
because if you understand that people
take have different views based on
product in instinctive temperaments
inbuilt temperaments then you start to
get a meta perspective let naturally
that there are different perspectives
and different perspectives have
different values I love what Jordan
Greenhalgh said I think it was in the
original glitch in the matrix film where
he said that what we've done through
social media is we are splitting off
into tribes based on temperament and
that could be an extinction airy
trajectory because we're only
particularly effective in groups of
mixed temperament that's how we're built
with designs to work together in groups
of mixed temperament and what we've done
is kind of weaponized temperament
against each other and then polarize
into these different fragment
groups and that could very well be an
extinction airy trajectory for the
mankind I think that's a really
beautiful kind of idea of how a
splitting society now we've started
talking about integral theory I think
it's good to to bring in Ken Wilbur's
framing because I think it really talks
very well to what's going on
particularly with what he calls green
postmodern liberal consciousness and why
it's basically in his view kind of
collapsed in on itself which i think is
is played out perfectly and what we've
seen with with the corbin wave and how
it's now kind of collapsing on itself
what's getting left out is you have this
green multicultural Michalik arianism
that's being taken to such extremes it's
really becoming absolute istic in its
view so you have absolute istic to
multiplicity to relativistic and the
problem with relativistic is it becomes
very open to what's called performative
contradictions becomes very open to self
contradictory statements it does it
almost all the time so element came for
example that it is universally
undeniably true that there is no
universal truth it will maintain that
all knowledge is social construction
it's all an interpretation it all
depends upon which culture it's arising
in and yet everything that I just said
that represents the green point of view
it maintains that it's view is not
culturally constructed it's true for all
people at all places at all time it's
not a matter of interpretation it's got
real truth nobody else has truth his
objective truth doesn't exist
but that view itself is held to be
objectively true by the post modernist
so they do get caught up in this
enormous kind of contradiction and they
do tend to absolute eyes their view
there are two ways you can end up at
Absolute
mystic beliefs one is that you're just
on your way up through the growth stages
yourself and you're at that stage and
people by the way you can stay at those
states the entire adult life the fact
that we have higher stage doesn't mean
that you have to develop there it's one
of the problems but so they'll have that
AB statistic view just because they're
on the way of passing through it but if
at any higher stage you latch on to
review with such absolute uncritical
absolutism you can start to request to
the actual absolutist ik stage because
that's where you feel right that's where
you feel yeah this is I know I've got it
right this is it say end up regressing
to an absolutist ik ethnocentric stage
and a problem with that is that it is
ethnocentric it is tribal and identity
politics lends itself to tribalism
because what you're emphasizing is your
particular tribe and you'll know if
you're doing that from a world Sentri
stance if when you talk about your tribe
in addition to whatever important
differences there are you also talk
about what your tribe has in common with
all the other tribes then that's world
center there's a unity and diversity
with that but if you just talk about
your tribe and how it's different from
all the other tribes and is there some
sort of special attention is gas
ethnocentric absolutist ik tribalism so
I think ken wilber point around this
kind of absolutism that comes with these
developmental stages is really key
because each of the stages up until the
second here when when people we become
able to see and hold multiple
perspectives each stage up until then
the argument goes tends to think it's
right it's like I'm right about the way
I see the world and
it's impossible to see in any weather
way we're the good guys you know they
can that's something I see very often I
think in any election that bad cap comes
up and there is a paradox in so integral
is the idea in integral is that were
able to see in appreciate multiple
perspectives the paradox is that green
postmodern thinks that it often thinks
that it's integral but you see that
stages thing all the time the Green
thinks that it's integral because it it
will accept people from whatever
background from whatever gender
sexuality it as all equal and that's a
valuable perspective but they mistake
that for being integral because
ultimately there's actually a hidden
tribalism there because their other ring
and rejecting anyone that doesn't agree
with them about their particular
perspective they don't actually
understand and the paradox is a lot of
the people that they are being inclusive
towards probably don't share their views
or most certainly don't share their
views if you're going to be like very
inclusive towards immigrants from
everywhere around the world you're going
to be being inclusive towards a lot of
people with very traditional values and
that's a hugely that's a that's a very
weird position to find yourself in which
is why you end up in a position in the
UK election where all the people that
supposedly you are supporting like
you're saying oh we're for the many
we're supporting all of the working
class we're supporting all of the
downtrodden it's like well they've told
you to fuck off they've pretty much
universally turned around so we don't
want your faux compassion we don't want
your condescension we don't want your
student politics masquerading as virtue
we don't want your virtue signaling we
want we want people to understand our
values who value what we value which and
David Goodheart said this really well
when he talked about somewheres and
anywheres like a really good definition
is likely anywheres are you identify
with your achievement so your degree
your profession that you can take
anywhere around the world you sort of
you're you're liberated from space and
place and then the somewheres are much
more rooted in a place an identity
that's tied to being like a Cornish
fishermen or a Welsh miner or
I knew and you're much more asset you're
somewhere not in anywhere and that
division has become huge especially with
Breck setting us you especially in the
UK and that's the one that's been sort
of underneath a lot of the what we're
seeing with being rejected by the UK
left or with labour being rejected by
the UK electorate I think another good
point in that is that the anywhere is
tend to live in the big cities in London
New York Paris wherever and somewheres
tend to live in the countryside so we
see in America in the UK this huge
divide between the kind of metropolitan
cities and the values at play and the
countryside which is again what's a big
shocker for people in a particular kind
of London filter bubble where London for
example votes mainly labour to see the
rest of the country really thinks
differently there's just one point
around one idea from integral studies I
think it's also quite useful to bring in
to this conversation which is a pre
trans fallacy so to take your point
before about something like immigration
right so from a level of development
which cares about me my family my tribe
say like read in that model the the
natural response might be close the
borders it's just us we're gonna isolate
and then Green might have the
perspective of no let's let everyone in
what is the nation anyway let's play
with this let's kind of deconstruct that
which is also a natural stage and then
the next level up is the more nuanced
level where it goes
hang on maybe we should have some
restrictions and maybe in this situation
it's like this and other situations like
that the pre trans fallacy is really
useful but it points out that the the
tends to go for example should there be
in that example
should there be limited immigration it
goes yes from that red tribalist yes
there should be because I wanna protect
me in my family then the Green goes no
and then again the more nuanced
perspective might say kind of yes but
also no so people confuse the two so as
soon as you for example mention well
actually I think sometimes immigration
is like you're one of them you know so
that pre trans fallacy is a really core
concept I encourage it you know it's a
kind of a big concept to research but I
find it particularly useful for
something like this because it can kind
of clarify a lot of where a lot of
reactivity comes from where it doesn't
necessarily
to be and I want to put in a little clip
from Diane musho Hamilton as well the
Zen priests mediator and also expert on
integral theory and she she uses the
integral map because the integral map
basically from these sort of red to
green to integral is about how many
perspectives you including are you able
to are you you start from the egocentric
to a family to world centric perspective
and it's really a developmental journey
of how many how many perspectives can
you incorporate into your view and you
also hold multiple perspectives now
right here gets a little bit dicey
because some of these communication
skills correlate to what we we talk
about when we talk about human
development it is not a given that
everyone in the room can hold two
perspectives in their body mind at the
same time without an overabundance of
chaos and tension and will naturally
collapse into one so one of the ways
that I became engaged with ken wilber an
integral Institute is in my work as a
mediator particularly around difficult
conversations like race and gender and
social justice and those kinds of things
is I started to observe real differences
in people's capacities some people
couldn't take their own perspective
they'd either been abused or
marginalized some people could take one
perspective their own but not the other
some people could take their own and
even start to be able to hear the
perspective of others but couldn't take
a perspective of a court or a judge and
that was literally that observation I
started to use a stage model in my own
work and so related to what Diane was
saying as well as this concept that
we've talked law about on the channel
which is the shadow so the shadow and
union psychology is all those aspects of
ourselves that we reject and push away
and say that's not me but in the process
we project out on to the other and it
comes out as a kind of disgust and we
see it in politics all the time the
whole process of uttering people is very
much a shadow process all they have
there's some aspect of myself that I
hate and that person's got it but I
don't have it but I'm I'm a good guy and
Young famously said that none of us are
as good a person as we think we are you
know so big part of development is to
look at those aspects of ourselves and I
think
no one explains that better than dojin
Roshi of course people don't want to do
it the the addiction and post modernity
seems to be wanting to feel good you
know you can't do the deeper work if
you're limited to feeling good that
there was a Buddhist team you blame the
baby boomers for that no we can't blame
anybody we have to take responsibility
blaming won't health or not it's part of
the problem we must take responsibility
the rescuer the victim and the
perpetrator this is an endless cycle in
post modernity they are identified with
the rescuer which is really deep down
it's the Savior the archetype of the
Savior now how deep are those roots in
Christian soil the victim is the
sacrificial lamb who must be sacrificed
and stay sacrificed no redemption and
the perpetrator becomes the scapegoat
that in the Talmud the Old Testament was
loaded up with the sins of the people
and chased into the desert to die the
scapegoat the one that carried the
burdens which meant we had to we had to
account for our sins on the Day of
Atonement Yom Kippur my favorite holiday
so we must add something to this trilogy
to make it whole and complete and what
we had and integrals in is the witness
who sees everything the whole dynamics
the rescuer keeps the victim stuck in
perpetual victimhood
unable to take responsibility and
projects their own responsibility blames
the scapegoat there's also something
Jonathan hike talks about which is how
polarization and division has grown and
he looks at sort of political mapping
and how they used to be an overlap we
might be show this picture at least to
be of an overlap between the two sides
and now they're getting more and more
apart and but the key part of that is is
not so much that they have different
views as what they think of the other
side and how in the last 20 years and
especially it seems like over the last
few years since the beginning of social
media like now it's not just this side
is is wrong and I disagree it's this
side is evil there's something
definitively wrong with these people who
are they we don't even understand
they're not even human that kind of
sense and that's the real danger is
where do you go when that starts
becoming your kind of the way you think
about the other side then where do you
end up you end up is in pretty nasty
places pretty quickly and there's a lot
of people feeling that things are
getting far more concerning if we can't
find our common humanity and at least
start having conversations where we
start understanding and seeing each
other as human rather than different I
mean there's something quite there's
something quite interesting in that for
me that just comes up which is the
slippery slope the kind of the movement
from there this is a kind of a fringe
it's not really you know there's a few
really extreme thinking people but I
think what's very important for everyone
all of us to be aware of is that if
we're not really aware of our language
or rhetoric how we other people then
we're all susceptible to a slippery
slope in that way now I've been seeing
people hearing people parties or
wherever talking about people on the
other side talking about Tories for
example as scum like scum dirt they're
not worth like that like they're not
human and it's like it astonishes me
because because the the the performative
contradiction of saying you're the good
guys and we're the inclusive people and
we care about the other people and we're
the nice ones and everyone else is so
mean and never and then in the same
breath dehumanizing anyone who disagrees
with you it boggles my mind and frankly
you're not progressed
if you're not progressive like that you
like and it is essential this is why the
shadow is such an important concept it
is essential that we all understand that
we are all capable of being Mia pressure
you know like it's just and have that
within us
it's and the hubris narcissism and
arrogance of thinking anything else is
astonishing and ends in tears I think a
lot of that after this election kind of
people ranting on social medium it's not
just the Tories or the opposition it's
also now blaming the people like blaming
the British people for rejecting labor
like all the people are stupid the peope
it's like this is this isn't incredible
like the arrogance of that is incredible
and also it ties into virtue signaling
as well and in the piece that we're
about to release with daniel
trachtenberg of the war on sense-making
- he makes a really interesting little
digression about virtue signaling like
what virtue signaling is compared to
what it and like what genuine virtue is
I'd like to play one way that I think of
the distinction between real virtue and
virtue signaling is virtue signaling is
when it's clear that an enough people
hold a particular trait as a virtue that
if I seem to have that virtue it would
be good for me right the people would
like me accept me agree with me buy my
stuff like my ideas whatever it is so if
I signal if I communicate in some way
that I have that virtue it's beneficial
for me in straight self-serving ways
right so I have a reason to signal the
virtue beyond my authentic living of it
a real virtue is something that is that
I care about that I value actually
hopefully something that is sacred to me
that I am willing to experience personal
sacrifice for not that my signalling of
it creates personal gain but I am
willing to lose personal gain in service
of this because it's more important than
personal gain to me so yeah hopefully
for me at least this can be a kind of
blank slate like I've seen so much
enthusiasm and
fashioned from a lot of my friends kind
of energized by either Jeremy Corbyn or
by kind of the Labour Party and
progressive politics which i think is
fantastic
for me they've been taken advantage of
frankly like these are Corbin and
McDonnell and Mill and Andrew Murray
those kind of people like the old guard
of the sort of 1970s leftists have
basically been the recipients of some
really well-meaning and great energy
that could go towards a good cause and I
think they've kind of taken advantage of
it so I am hoping that this kind of
we'll be able to all of that energy and
all of that potential for change can now
be put into something more valuable yeah
and for me it's very much I like the
idea of a blank slate because I think
like rebel wisdom is in many ways a
process of inquiry and so it's like I
don't know where to go next I don't know
where what all the different I don't
know what direction we need to go but I
think we've had a lot of people on the
channel talking about pieces of that
puzzle you know and so there's a lot of
and that inquiry is ongoing so my hope
is that and it kind of begins with a
sense of humility that we all have to
just say okay we're not quite sure the
world is very different now there's many
different routes we could go in
certainly my hope is that it moves
towards somewhere more empathetic where
we don't all have to agree but at least
we can kind of create something through
our disagreement instead of it just kind
of polarizing us in little bubbles so my
hope is that kind of some kind of like
opening up and less rigidity and an
openness to different perspectives
there's at least part of you know what
might drive us forward somewhere it
decently and if you've made it this far
congratulations let us know what you
think in the comment
and zhuzhing rebel wisdom is a new sense
making platform bringing together the
most rebellious and inspiring thinkers
from around the world if you're enjoying
our content then you can help us make
more by becoming a subscriber which will
give you access to a load of exclusive
films also you can then join our group
zoom calls to discuss the ideas in the
films and you can send us ideas for
questions for upcoming interviews we're
also looking for talented people to help
us out with editing graphics music that
kind of thing and if you're a regular
viewer you'll know we talked a lot about
the value of embodying or actually
living out the ideas that we talk about
so that's why we run regular events in
London check out the links on the
website for more and hope to see you
soon
you